http://www.comtekadvanced.com/privacy

Privacy
By using this website, You agree to Our Terms of Use. Read them here.“Comtek”, “We” or “Us” means Comtek Advanced Structures Ltd., a company duly incorporated under the laws of Canada. “You”, “Yourself” or “Your” shall mean you, the user of this website. Comtek respects the privacy of personal information and is committed to protecting personal information that We handle.Visitors to this website are not requested to reveal any personal information; however, You may provide personal information to Us on a voluntary basis while using certain website features, such as the Contact section and Careers section of this website. If You submit an enquiry to this website, any personal information You submit will only be used by employees of Comtek who We reasonably believe require access to the information to respond to Your inquiry.Comtek will never share, disclose or transfer Your personal information to any third party other than our subsidiaries without Your permission, unless We are required to do so by law. Although safe guards are in place to provide data security, We cannot guarantee that such information will not be lost or used unlawfully as data transmission over the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be completely confidential. Comtek disclaims liability for any use that may be made of the information by You or any third party.Account Information No user account features exist on Comtek's website and as such no personal information is stored, and ability to edit and delete a user account is inapplicable.CookiesComtek uses analytics tools to collect information about how visitors use this website. Through analytics cookies, information is stored to create information about the user experience, such as what pages people visit, how long they are on the site, how they got there and what they click on. Information supplied by cookies helps us ensure our site is meeting the needs of visitors and to find ways to provide a better experience.Analytics cookies do not collect or store user's personal information, such as names or addresses, and cannot be used to identify individuals.External Links This website may contain links that take You to other websites. This privacy statement does not extend to the data collection practices of these websites and Comtek does not assume any responsibility for the privacy practices, policies or actions of third parties.Changes to this Privacy Policy Comtek reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time.
Comtek designs, manufactures and repairs aircraft components with a focus on improved durability and shorter lead times. Using advanced out-of-autoclave technologies, we develop composite solutions that reduce part weight, lower total costs, and shorten production cycles.
Site Map  |
Terms of Use  |
Privacy © Comtek Advanced Structures Ltd. 2020
Share by:
